CHRISTOPHER HAGE

6/20 RIDDELL ROAD, HOLDEN HILL 5088; 0422638193; CHAGES16@GMAIL.COM; D.O.B: 16/10/1985

OBJECTIVE

Full Stack developer in training currently looking to utilise my management background and my past creative pursuits to assist upcoming and established businesses in order to develop and simplify their applications. Currently developing my skills as a Full-stack developer with Adelaide University, I'm learning to be proficient in Javascript, JQuery, CSS, and multiple Third Party and Server-Side APis as well as responsive and adaptive web-design. I enjoy solving problems and finding creative solutions to improve productivity and user experience.

My goal is to utilise the skills I have developed in my coding course, and integrate them with the leadership and customer service skills I have gained as a Frontline Manager and Sales Person over the last 11 years at TPG to the best of my ability. I plan to find a suitable career with a respectable employer where I can use my knowledge to develop and maintain internal applications.

EXPERIENCE

2020 CODING BOOTCAMP Adelaide, SA

STUDENT*

- Learning Javascript, JQuery, CSS and HTML applications
- Proficient at integrating API functionality,
- Main project- designed an app to search movie information based on a user's search input
- Maintained an average A grade from coursework and projects.

2019 UNITI WIRELESS Adelaide, SA

CUSTOMER SERVICE OFFICE

- Technical Support For Wireless and Fixed Line Services
- Billing Enquiries
- Cancellation and Retention Enquiries
- Responding to Emails

14/11/2016 TO 16/02/2019 TPG

Adelaide, SA

- BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT MANAGER

 Competitive Sales environment- Corporate Grade IP Services
 - Identify Solutions that would assist in improving Business day to day efficiency
 - Retention
 - Corporate Account Management- Billing, Support, Service Delivery
 - Face to Face client meetings
 - Training and coaching of new staff
 - Assistance in migration to new infrastructure and services
 - Worked closely with Channel Partner team and resellers to assist clients

17/5/2013 TO 14/11/2016 iiNet Adelaide, SA

BUSINESS SALES CUSTOMER SERVICE MANAGER

- Training, mentoring and coaching CSRs
- Introducing team members to Adherence, ACW
- Implementing NPS for the team-Exceeding targets over the last 4 months and winning an internal NPS competition within the BCC.

- Performance Management
- Efficiently handling escalations and TIO complaints
- Implementation of NPS and Conversion Rate competitions for the Business team
- Exceeded all Adherence, NPS and Conversion rate targets for the H1 2014
- Increased Team NPS from 30% to 70%
- Promoting company and NBN at Victor Harbor Business Conference

29/6/2009 TO 17/5/2013

Internode/ iiNet

Adelaide, SA

BUSINESS SALES TEAM LEADER

- Reporting to the National Sales Manager
- Implemented Outbound Sales Campaigns
- · Assisted with the introduction of a commission-based incentive plan within the department
- Created and altered processes, including the Relocation process in order to improve efficiency
- Training, mentoring and coaching staff.
- Ran Business Sales product trainings for CSRs in other departments
- Generated reporting systems using Excel in order to save time collating data for the team
- Maintained Rosters for the team without the support of the WFM department.

19/6/2007 TO 26/6/2009

Internode

Adelaide, SA

SALES REPRESENTATIVE

- Selling ADSL, VOIP, DNS, Webhosting to Business and Residential customers
- Sales Person of The Quarter Residential Sales July-September 2007
- Sales Person of The Quarter Residential Sales October-December 2007

EDUCATION

2020 CODING BOOTCAMP

University of Adelaide

Adelaide, SA

2011

CERTIFICATE IV FRONTLINE MANAGEMENT

2004-2007

University of Adelaide

Adelaide, SA

BACHELOR OF MEDIA

REFERENCES

Bill Elsaved- 0447 348 880

Further TPG, iiNet and Internode References are available on request.